Guide to the Ben Morea and Aldo Tambellini Papers TAM.530
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VIII: Oversize Materials, 1962-1969
  - D. Publications of groups in NY and London connected or relevant to Ben Morea and the Up Against the Wall Motherfucker "affinity groups,"
    - Untitled Issue [incomplete] of Newspaper: Lead Article "1...2...3...Many Bostons" (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Evo article by Alex Gross on "Artists Attack Moma.", undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Up Against the Wall Motherfucker comic in The East Village Other, December 27, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - SDS New Left Notes (January 22, 1969, p. 2): Article on Ben Morea's acquittal (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - "King Mob: Two Letters On Student Power" [four page broadside] published in London as a supplement to King Mob Echo, Nov 1968 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Sansculottes issues 25 & 29, published by the Free Youth Press (a high-school group influenced by the Motherfuckers and the SI)., undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Sundance (First issue); by the White Panther Information Service. Headline: "YOUTH WILL MAKE THE REVOLUTION AND YOUTH WILL KEEP IT!" Oversize full-color 32-page paper, edited by David Sinclair. Sinclair's opening poem ends with: "in my dreams I hear the triumph of my forest speech in another time, and it says, with a vengeance, Up Against the Wall Motherfuckers!", undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Logos, Oversize full color paper with centerfold on "Revolutionary Ecology." Text by Murray Bookchin., undated (Box 4, Folder 25)